<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wattpad</string>
    <string name="label_title">Last Stories</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Stories You’ll Love</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">
        Whatever you’re into, there is something you’ll love on Wattpad. \n
        And if you can’t find exactly what you’re looking for, you have the power to create it yourself.
    </string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Storytelling Redefined</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">
        Wattpad takes everything you love about storytelling, and turns it into a social, on-the-go experience.
        The result is a one-of-a-kind adventure in creation and discovery.
        Today, the global Wattpad community is made up of more than 65 million people.
        We’re proudly based in Toronto, Canada, but Wattpad stories transcend borders, interests, and language.
    </string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">A Captivated Audience</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">
        In a world of 7-second attention spans, people everywhere still long to be immersed in content that matters to them.
        The Wattpad community collectively spends an incredible 15 billion minutes each month using Wattpad.
    </string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Freedom to Discover and Create</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">
        Wattpad gives people from around the world access to an audience of millions, and connects them with content they can’t find anywhere else.
        You can discover the things that speak to you, or choose to create them from scratch.
        It’s the freedom to express yourself with an authentic voice, and the knowledge that you will be heard.
    </string>

    <string name="slide_5_title">Read offline</string>
    <string name="slide_5_desc">
        After your first use, the Wattpad App will provide you some content for using offline, as soon as you connect to the internet
        again and open the App, new data will be loaded.
    </string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> Wattpad -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>

    <string name="next_button_title">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip_button_title">SKIP</string>
    <string name="done_button_title">FINISH</string>

</resources>
